export const Surveydata = [
    {
        id: "1",
        question: "What is GreenFlow Nexus?",
        answer: "GreenFlow Nexus is a platform that supports Nigerian farmers and agriculture enthusiasts by providing sustainable solutions, market access, and community-driven resources to reduce post-harvest losses and promote food security."
    },
    {
        id: "2",
        question: "Who can join GreenFlow Nexus?",
        answer: "GreenFlow Nexus is open to anyone interested in sustainable agriculture, including students, experienced farmers, and individuals passionate about making a positive impact on the food system."
    },
    {
        id: "3",
        question: "How can I join the GreenFlow Nexus community?",
        answer: "You can join our community by filling out the application form linked on our website. Once you’re onboard, you’ll gain access to exclusive resources, events, and networking opportunities."
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "What kind of support does GreenFlow Nexus offer farmers?",
        answer: "GreenFlow Nexus provides farmers with tools to reduce post-harvest losses, training in sustainable practices, and access to a network of resources and buyers. Our goal is to make farming more efficient and profitable for all members."
    },
    {
        id: "5",
        question: "Are there any fees to join GreenFlow Nexus?",
        answer: "Currently, joining the GreenFlow Nexus community is free! We are here to support and empower farmers and agriculture enthusiasts at all stages."
    },
    {
        id: "6",
        question: "What types of resources are available on the platform?",
        answer: "Members have access to a range of resources, including sustainable farming guides, training programs, networking events, and market access opportunities.."
    },
    {
        id: "7",
        question: "Is GreenFlow Nexus only for Nigerian farmers?",
        answer: "While our primary focus is on supporting African farmers, our community welcomes anyone interested in sustainable agricultural practices in similar climates and regions"
    },
    {
        id: "8",
        question: "How does GreenFlow Nexus help with market access?",
        answer: "GreenFlow Nexus connects farmers with buyers, enabling easier sales and reduced post-harvest losses. By bridging the gap between farmers and the market, we help ensure that farmers receive fair value for their produce."
    },
    {
        id: "9",
        question: "What role does Sahel Consulting play in GreenFlow Nexus?",
        answer: "Sahel Consulting supports GreenFlow Nexus by providing guidance, resources, and expertise to ensure our projects align with sustainable food systems and food security goals."
    },
    {
        id: "10",
        question: "How can I get involved if I’m not a farmer?",
        answer: "There are many ways to get involved with GreenFlow Nexus. You can join as a volunteer, participate in events, contribute your skills, or support our initiatives to strengthen food systems in Nigeria."
    },
]

export const perishableData = [ 
    "Fruits",
    "Vegeatables", 
    "Root and Tuber Crops",
    "Legumes",
    "Other perishable"
]